# SASWATA CHATTERJEE

#### S O F T W A R E E N G I N E E R



9007950520



chatterjeesaswata1997@gmail.com



Kolkata



https://fastidious-cranachan-5245b3.netlify.app/

### **PROFILE**

Innovative and curious computer science engineer with a desire to always learn new things and apply them to real world scenarios in beneficial ways.

 $Skilled\ in\ JavaScript, Cs, HTML, Java\ and\ python\ and\ continuously\ trying\ to\ improve\ upon\ these\ , Also\ learning\ react\ .$ 

Committed to working as a collaborative and positive team member, striving to utilize my knowledge and expertise to optimize engineering results.

### SKILLS

- · Web Design
- Javascript
- HTML/CSS
- JAVA
- Python
- React js
- · Problem-Solving
- Front End Coding

### EXPERIENCE

#### **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

Intelligent Inspiration

2020-2022

Monitored various automation processes and fixed errors in real time to ensure smooth flow of processes.

Occasionally wrote bash scripts to automate simple and redundant tasks . Solved error tickets and provided support.

#### **DATA ANALYST**

Globsyn 3rd life

2014 - 2016

Interned while in college as a data analyst was in charge of data annotation for Al models.

### ACHIEVMENTS

Machine Learning Model

2019

Won best project award as a group for building a forest fire prediction model using python frameworks and machine learning .

## LANGUAGES

English, Bengali, Hindi, Arabic,

German

# EDUCATION

### **BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY**

Graduated with a d.g.p.a of 8.4 in computer science engineering from Elitte College of Engineering

2016-2020

#### ISC

Graduated from St Augustine;s Day School scoring 89%

2016

### **ICSE**

Scored 91 % from St Augustine;s Day SChool

2014